前情提要
Previously on "The 100"...
一旦我们杀掉那些普莱姆  我们就能接管圣所
Once we kill their Primes, we take over Sanctum.
是你的主意  还是暗黑指挥官的
I that your idea or Sheidheda's?
要是管用  谁在乎
Who cares if it works?
- 乔丹  - 把这孩子和其他人关在一起
- Jordan? - Lock the child up with the others.
克拉克还活着
JOSEPHINE: Clarke's alive,
但我们共享的这个大脑  正在死亡
but the brain we now share is dying.
找到加百列  他是他们中的一员
Find Gabriel. He was one of them.
- 注意安全  - 去救克拉克
- BELLAMY: Stay safe. - ECHO: Save Clarke.
他们不说
JADE: They're not talking.
把他们和其他人关一起
Put them with the others.
是约瑟芬
It's Josephine.
克拉克  她把控制权给你了  你得跑了
Clarke, she gave you control? You got to run.
不  我不会丢下你的
No. I'm not leaving you.
去找到加百列
Go find Gabriel now!
我为什么能看见你
Why can I see you?
因为情况变得更糟了
Because it's getting worse.
把控制权还给我  反正等你睡着的时候
Give me back control. I'll just get it anyway
我也能要回来的
when you fall asleep.
你现在要做什么
What are you doing now?
加百列  我叫克拉克·格里芬
Gabriel, my name is Clarke Griffin.
约瑟芬·莱特伯恩在我的脑子里
Josephine Lightbourne is in my head.
如果你能听到  我们过来找你了
If you can hear this, we're coming to you.
小心点  我们现在离营地很近了
JOSEPHINE: Be careful. We're close to the camp now.
加百列听到引擎的声音  他就会
When Gabriel hears the engines, he'll...
安静  我要集中精神
CLARKE: Quiet. I'm concentrating.
告诉过你  该让我来的
JOSEPHINE: Told you I should drive.
现在你要把控制权给我了吗
Now will you give me back control,
还是说要我等到你睡着
or do I have to wait until you fall asleep?
闭嘴  我得呼叫加百列
Shut up. I have to call Gabriel.
那玩意你也摔坏了
Yeah. You broke that, too.
- 我得躲起来  - 我们做个交易
- I have to hide. - OK. Here's the deal.
如果我们回去圣所
If we go back to Sanctum,
我就把身体还给你
I'll give you your body back.
好吧  那就等到我的护卫们找到我们
Fine! We can just wait for my guards to find us.
应该用不了多久的
It shouldn't be long now.
我们不知道那些是你的人
We don't know that they're your people.
要是加百列的子嗣干掉了你的护卫呢
What if the Children of Gabriel took out your guards?
我是说  他们战斗力很烂
I mean, they do kind of suck.
你想要冒险  让我们都丢掉脑袋吗
You want to risk losing our head?
我对天发誓  要是你撒谎
I swear to God, if you're lying,
我会亲手把思维驱动器取出来
I'll take out the mind drive myself
并在我死前毁掉它
and destroy it before I die.
别那么紧张  放松
Yeesh. Tense much? Relax.
让你的眼睛四处看看  这样我也能看到
Just keep your eyes moving all around so I can see.
我们在找  这个
We're looking for... this.
把树叶清理掉  你就能找到舱门了
Clear the leaves. You'll find a hatch.
戴上头盔  准备好枪
MAN: Whoa.
这是敌人的树林
WOMAN: Keep your helmets on and your guns ready.
我想我的护卫们也没那么烂
These are the enemy's woods.
别那样了
I guess my guards don't suck after all, huh?
引擎还是热的
Stop doing that.
她不会太远
MAN: The engine's still warm.
在补给箱里应该会有
She can't be far.
灯或是火柴什么的
There should be a light or some matches in the supply kit.
在他们走之前  我们都在这趴低
We lay low here until they pass.
然后我们步行
Then we go on foot.
分散一点
MAN: Spread out a little bit.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
暗哨  我们在四处建了很多
Observation blind. We built them all over.
我用他们来研究自然栖息地的物种
I use them to study species in their natural habitat.
研究
Studying, huh?
研究很是无聊
Research can get boring.
加百列帮了我
Gabriel helped with that.
你们看起来有很多故事
You guys seem to have a lot of history.
为什么他现在想杀你了
Why does he want to kill you now?
- 他不想  - 真的吗  都说普莱姆去死了
- He doesn't. - Really? Death to Primes?
不然我差点就信了
Could have fooled me.
不是那意思
It's not literal.
加百列的子嗣们自以为醒悟了
The Children of Gabriel consider themselves enlightened,
一次释放一个思维
freeing minds one at a time.
在他离开后的70年里
In the 70 years since he left,
其实他们没有杀死任何普莱姆
they've killed exactly no Primes.
他为什么离开
Why did he leave?
他想要死去
He wanted to be able to die.
而我不想  就这么简单
I didn't. Simple as that.
为什么  你在想什么
Why? What are you thinking?
我在想  没那么简单
I'm thinking it's not as simple as that.
我在想
I'm thinking
他对偷尸失去了兴趣
that he lost his taste for body snatching,
看在我们的交情上  我希望
and I'm hoping for all our sakes
他不会把你的思维驱动拿出来后
that he doesn't destroy your mind drive
就立马摧毁了
as soon as he takes it out.
贝拉米的计划
Hmm. Bellamy's plan...
救你  然后用我的思维驱动换你们的人
save you, trade my drive for your people.
这意味着让你复活
It would mean letting you resurrect again.
他会这么做吗  他还爱你吗
Would he do it? Does he still love you?
克拉克
Clarke?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
克拉克  不  不  不
Clarke? No, no. No, no, no.
现在不行  我们会困在这的
Not now. We'll be stuck here.
藤蔓会过来的  我说的睡觉不是这意思
The vines will come. This is not what I meant by falling asleep.
与它抗争到底  克拉克  否则我会
Fight through it, Clarke, or I'll be locked
永远被锁在你脑袋的驱动里
inside a drive, inside your head,
锁在这个盒子里
inside this box forever.
我们完蛋了
We're so screwed.
地 球 百 子
第六季        第十集
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
翻译： 瑟瑟谷中风
翻译： 噬魂师
翻译： 岛岛
翻译： 文睿
校对： 噬魂师
时间轴/特效：小螺号
统筹：Kate
总监：麦斯
西蒙妮会想为凯恩报仇的
RAVEN: Simone's gonna want payback for Kane.
我们找到我们的人   然后回到
Let's just get our people and go back to the...
这可不是好事
This can't be good.
我们的新普莱姆在哪
Where's our new Prime?
那个傻瓜自杀了  浪费了一个好的思维驱动
SIMONE: The fool killed himself, wasting a good mind drive.
这里怎么了
What happened here?
我们现在能做夜血了吗
Can we make the blood or not?
- 把他们和其他人关在一起  - 好的  先生
- Put them with the others! - Yes, sir.
怎么回事
Hey. What... what is this?
放开我
Hey. Get off me!
- 走吧  - 快走
- Let's go. - Get to it.
等等
Wait.
有件事我一直想告诉你
There's something I've been meaning to tell you.
他不想让你知道
He doesn't want you to know this,
你的女儿也死了
but your daughter is dead, too.
什么
What?
我说了  把他们带走
I said take them.
你在说什么
RAVEN: Oh. Hey! What are you talking about?
不  等等  不
No! Wait! No!
这可不合适  西蒙妮
That was unkind, Simone,
而且这也不完全是真的
and not exactly true.
克拉克的思维活了下来
Clarke's mind survived the procedure.
她的朋友们知道后  送她过了屏障
Her friends found out and got her past the shield.
我派了人去搜索树林
I have teams searching the woods,
并把她的人当作是人质
and I'm holding her people as insurance.
人质
Insurance?
我们的女儿不见了  我们家变成了一个武装基地
Our daughter is gone, our home is an armed encampment.
我们就不该让他们留下的
We should have never let them stay.
你说得对  是我的错
You're right. This is my fault,
我正在处理
and I'm dealing with it.
你还有什么没告诉我
What else aren't you telling me?
为什么圣所处于一级防范禁闭
Why is Sanctum on lockdown?
米兰达死了
Miranda's dead,
被那个孩子宿主杀了  克拉克的女儿
killed by the child host, Clarke's daughter.
我们把她和他们中大多数人关在了一起
We have her in custody with most of the others,
但还有两个没抓到
but two of them are still at large.
我们相信他们还在圣所
We believe they're in Sanctum,
这就是我们封闭的原因
which is why we're on lockdown.
要是有人把他们藏起来  那仅仅封锁是不够的
Lockdown isn't enough if someone is hiding them.
拉塞尔  这些人知道我们的真相
Russell, these people know the truth about us.
把这些传播给我们的人民要多久
How long till it spreads to our people
他们还会跟随我们吗
and they come after us?
必须杀鸡儆猴
An example must be made.
如果你觉得我会处死孩子
If you think I'm executing a child...
不是那孩子  她有夜血
Not the child. She has the blood.
我们烧死其他人  找出是谁帮忙
We burn the rest, we find out who was helping to hide the other two,
藏了其他两个人  然后也烧死他们
and they burn with them.
听听你自己说的
Shh, shh, shh, shh. Listen to yourself.
我知道你的感受  我也是如此
I know how you feel. I feel it, too,
但要是我们这么做  我们就没有
but if we do that, we leave nothing left
换回约瑟芬的筹码了
to bargain for Josephine,
而我们会变得和他们一样
and we will have become just like them.
看看你的周围  亲爱的
Look around you, my love.
圣所的梦想已经死了
The dream of Sanctum is already dead,
但因为我信你  我们只杀一个
but because I trust you, we'll only kill one.
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
相信我  我希望我是的
Believe me, I wish I was,
但你的女儿不是普莱姆之一
but your daughter's not one with the Primes.
没人是
No one is.
我白白牺牲了
I sacrificed my baby boy...
我的孩子
for nothing.
我的妻子接受不了
My wife couldn't live with that.
一年后  她长眠于献祭林
She laid down in the Offering Grove a year later,
我仍然相信
and I still believed.
我相信着
I believed.
这不是谎言  乔丹试图告诉我们真相。
BLYTHE ANN: It's not a lie. Jordan tried to tell us the truth.
好吧  飞船已经就位  随时可以起飞
OK. The ship is back, the fuse is lit.
现在我们该怎么把我们的人带出去
Now how do we get our people out?
放松  革命需要时间
Relax. Revolutions take time.
我不在乎他们的革命
I don't care about their revolution.
我们得带指挥官离开这里
We need to get our Commander out of here.
她驱逐了你  但她仍是你的全部
She banished you. Still, she's all you are about.
我希望那些护卫更容易动摇
Let's hope the null guards are more easily swayed.
- 什么意思  - 意思是如果他们没有站起来
- Meaning what? - Meaning if they don't rise up
推翻他们虚假的神
and overthrow their false gods
一旦他们了解了真相
once they learn the truth,
我们需要一个B计划
we're gonna need a plan B.
所有人回到位置
RYKER: Everybody get in position.
怎么了
What is it?
好  去吧
All right. Go.
直接回你们住处去
Go directly back to your quarters.
如果有人拦着你  你就给他们看我的工作指令
If you get stopped, you show them my work orders.
等下  我们已经按你说的做了
Wait. What do we do with what you told us?
还不够  一旦足够多的人知道真相
Nothing yet. Once enough people know the truth,
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
我们可以和平地解决这事
we can change things peacefully.
和平的  嗯
ECHO: Peacefully, huh?
继续骗自己吧  赖克
Keep telling yourself that, Ryker.
怎么了  怎么回事
GAIA: What is it? What's wrong?
他们因为米兰达的死而要处决你们的一个人
They're executing one of your people tonight for killing Miranda.
- 麦迪 - 不，不会是她
- Madi? - No. Won't be her.
她是宿主
She's a host.
如果是我认识的西蒙妮  她会让他们自己 选择要死的人
If I know Simone, she'll let them choose who dies themselves.
我们如何阻止它
How do we stop it?
我们不阻止  我需要你在我的弓上加一个瞄准镜
We don't. I'll need you to add a scope to my bow
把我带到一个能看到
and get me to a window with a view
行刑的地方
of the execution.
- B计划  - 哇哦  等会
- Plan B. - Whoa. Slow down.
我不会让你去暗杀别人
You're not assassinating anyone.
我同意把你们藏起来  我同意告诉人们真相
I agreed to hide you, I agreed to tell people the truth.
你这么做是因为我威胁要揭发你
You did that because I threatened to expose you
你就是放走恶魔加百列的叛徒
as the traitor who let the demon Gabriel go free,
这就是你会这么做的原因
which is exactly why you'll do this.
赖克  承认吧
Ryker, admit it.
站对边的感觉很好
It feels good to be on the right side.
如果你失手了  我们的人就会死
If you miss, one of our people dies.
我不会失手
I won't miss.
那么他们会选择谁呢
So who will they choose?
很简单  墨菲
Well, that's easy. Murphy.
会是我  不是吗
It's gonna be me, isn't it?
就应该是你  叛徒
It should be you, traitor!
告诉过你
Told you.
她刺伤乔丹时  她的眼睛里也有同样的表情
Same look she had in her eyes when she stabbed Jordan.
我们还是聊聊当下的事情吧
MURPHY: Can we please get back to the fact
我们中的一个今晚会死吗
that one of us is gonna die tonight?
不会的
That's not gonna happen.
厄科会有办法的
Echo will think of something.
她为什么叫你叛徒
Why did she call you a traitor?
告诉她  叛徒
MADI: Tell her, traitor.
告诉她你是如何帮那个女孩 偷走她女儿的身体的
Tell her how you helped the girl who stole her daughter's body.
我以为她已经死了
I thought she was already dead.
艾比  他做了一笔交易来拯救我们大家
EMORI: Abby, he made a deal to save all of us.
当他发现她还活着时
When he found out she was still alive,
他做了正确的事
he did the right thing.
最终
Eventually.
你最好希望你的朋友厄科带我们离开这里
You better hope your friend Echo gets us out of here
因为如果她没有
because if she doesn't,
我们选择让你死
we choose you.
墙上那美酒佳酿  二十三瓶美酒
JOSEPHINE: ♪ Beer on the wall, 23 bottles of beer ♪
取下一瓶  递到你手
♪ Take one down, pass it around ♪
美酒只剩二十二瓶
♪ 22 bottles of beer on the wall ♪
约瑟芬
Josephine?
你不想看见我  看看这个
You don't want to see me? See this.
嘿
Hey.
Hey!
嘿
门
Door.
为什么你的记忆会在墙的另一边
Why are your memories on my side of the wall?
你知道为什么  我告诉过你把控制权给我
You know why. I told you to give me control.
现在太迟了
Now it's too late.
我们有多少时间
How much time do we have?
不多
Not much.
跟着我
Follow me.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要带你回你那边
I'm taking you back to your side.
你觉得我在哪
Where do you think I'm...
没什么那一边了
JOSEPHINE: There are no more sides.
不  不  离我远点
No, no! Get away from me!
离我远点  走开
Get away from me! Just get away!
离我远点
Get a... get away from me!
我的第二个身体
My second body.
我们之间的屏障正在瓦解
The barrier between our minds is breaking down.
不见得
You don't say.
听着  如果我们不快点
Look. If we don't think of something fast,
你就会死  而我会永远迷失
you die, and my mind drive is lost forever,
所以我们就别再互相讽刺了
so how about we cut the sarcasm and...
或者我可以再杀你一遍
Or I could just kill you again.
不要  没了去我那边的门
Don't. Without the door to my side,
我不知道我要去哪里  也不知道我会不会回来
I don't know where I'd go or if I'd come back.
这可能是永久的
It could be permanent.
这可不是坏事  为什么不开枪
And that's a bad thing why?
好吧  扣动扳机吧
Fine. Pull the trigger.
你要怎么做
What is it you say?
你自己去迷失吧
Go float yourself.
这就对了
That's it.
跟着我
Follow me.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
如果你是对的
If you're right, then in order to regain consciousness,
那么为了恢复意识  我们需要分离思想。
we need to separate our minds.
克拉克  这些是我的记忆
Clarke, those are my memories.
克拉克
Clarke!
要这个还是子弹
It's this or a bullet.
警告  15秒后会发生灾难性系统故障
COMPUTER: Warning. Catastrophic systems failure in 15...
来吧
- Do it. - 14...
13  12  11
13, 12,, 11,
10  9  8  7  6
10, 9, 8, 7, 6,
5...
起作用了  来  帮我
It worked. Come on. Help me.
这还不够  它们会一直流进来的
We have to do more. They'll keep bleeding through.
约瑟芬
Josephine.
我不记得你拿了什么
I don't... I don't remember what you took.
我只是
I just...
我知道它不见了
I know that it's gone.
警告  系统不稳定
COMPUTER: Warning. Systems critical.
听着  我们必须这样做
Look. We have to do this,
否则我们的大脑就会死亡
or our brain dies.
好吧  但我选择回忆
Fine, but I choose the memories.
你真的搞砸了
You really messed up.
是的  我知道
MURPHY: Yeah. I'm aware.
听着  我知道你要死了
RAVEN: Look. I know you're scared to die.
每个人都是
Everyone is,
但如果你想逃避地狱
but if you want to avoid hell,
答案不是不朽
the answer's not immortality.
是品行
It's morality.
开门
MAN: Open up.
在这儿等
Wait here.
- 我们走吧  - 放开我
- WOMAN: Let's go. - GAIA: Let go of me.
盖娅
Gaia!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
还以为你被驱逐了
Thought you were banished.
她是
She was!
我们有机会的时候就应该杀了你
We should have killed you when we had the chance.
别担心  指挥官  你很快就会有机会了
Don't worry, Heda. You'll get your chance soon
因为我们今晚都要离开这里
because we're all getting out of here tonight.
-  厄科 - 在行刑期间
- Echo? - During the execution.
别紧张  墨菲
Rest easy, Murphy.
今晚唯一要死的人是拉塞尔
The only person dying tonight is Russell.
赖克
RUSSELL: Ryker...
你心里有事
something on your mind?
是啊  嗯  我只是想知道
Yeah. Um,
我们什么时候开始重新处刑别人了
I was just wondering when we started executing people again.
别含糊其辞了  赖克
SIMONE: Oh, spare us your equivocation, Ryker.
你到底要说什么
What is that supposed to mean?
你很清楚那是什么意思
You know exactly what that means.
为了让你能坐在这里安心享受这顿饭
The lives that were taken so that you could be here
而被处死的人
enjoying this meal.
他们本不需要死去
They didn't deserve to die,
而你还对这一切有疑问
and yet now you have a problem executing a criminal?
我们能安静地吃午餐吗
Can we just eat lunch in peace?
拜托
Please.
西蒙妮  我们都对这一切感到不安
PRIYA: We are all upset with what's happened, Simone.
希望你们两个下一次
Hopefully next time, the two of you will involve us
能在情况失控之前找我们两个一起商量
in your decisions before they spiral out of control.
抱歉，但我有消息
Apologies, but I have news.
那个叫盖娅的人已经被抓获
The one they call Gaia has been captured.
我们把她和其他人关在了一起
We put her in with the others.
很好
RUSSELL: Well done.
这又是谁
And what have we here?
先生  他叫做泰  是一个声称
Sir, his name is Tai, a null who claims
知道他们最后一员  厄科躲在哪里
to know where the last of them... Echo... is hiding.
那为什么把他带过来
So why bring him here?
他不敢开口  先生
He's afraid to talk, sir.
我觉得在阁下您的面前
I thought he might be more inclined
他或许更愿意开口
to do so with your eminence.
好主意
A good thought.
带他上来吧
Bring him in.
你好啊  泰
Hello, Tai.
来坐  告诉我们你知道什么
Come. Sit. Tell us what you know.
你饿吗
Are you hungry?
不饿  谢谢
No, thank you.
我还是快点说吧
I should make this quick.
你要不要跟其中某一个单独谈谈
Perhaps you'd like to talk to one of us alone.
我所知道的
What I know...
或者我以为我所知道的
what I thought I knew
当我听从你孩子的命令
when I sacrificed my child
在献祭仪式上牺牲了我的孩子时
in the Offering Grove by your child's command
我以为你们都是神
was that you were all gods...
但你们不是
But you're not.
全部都是假的
It's all a lie,
如果这世界上还残存正义
and if there's any justice left in this world,
那你们的孩子也会死在同一片森林中
your child will die in those same woods.
你说什么
What did you just say?
住手  西蒙妮
-  - RUSSELL: No, no, no, no, no. Simone.
我说  普莱姆都要死
I said, "death to Primes!"
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
西蒙妮  快去找医生
RUSSELL: Simone! Get a doctor!
普莱姆都要死
Death to Primes!
快去找医生
RUSSELL: Get a doctor now!
普莱姆都要死  普莱姆都要死
TAI: Death to Primes! Death to Primes!
普莱姆都要死
Death to Primes!
我会把你带回来的
I'll bring you back.
无论需要付出什么代价
Whatever I have to do,
我会把你带回来的
I'll bring you back.
一定会把你带回来的
好了  老头  最后一个也准备好了
OK, old man. Last one's ready.
♪ You leapt from crumbling bridges... ♪
一开始的几天都会很奇怪
First few days are weird.
我没想这样
I didn't ask for this.
我知道的
I know,
但我不能失去你  加百利
but I couldn't lose you, Gabriel.
他们救我回来的时候
JOSEPHINE: His first body was already dying
他第一个身体已经因为癌症死亡了
from cancer when they brought me back.
我们来跳舞  看着吧
We're about to dance. Watch.
CIGARETTES AFTER SEX: ♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ Got the music in you, baby, tell me why ♪
约瑟芬
CLARKE: Josephine.
再让我看一下
Just let me watch a little more.
♪ You just can't say good-bye ♪
你呀
Hey.
你这新的躯体跳舞跳得还不错啊
This new body's got some rhythm.
♪ Foreheads of the lovers wrapped in your arms ♪
♪ You've been hiding them in... ♪
我们不能永远这样
Can't do this forever.
为什么
Why not?
我会爱你到永远的啊
It's how long I'll love you for.
♪ Got the music in you, baby, tell me why ♪
好吧  这个记忆你可以留下
OK. You can keep this one,
但如果你还想再见到他
but if you ever want to see him again,
我们现在就得走了
we have to move now.
他会想到办法救我们俩的
He'll find a way to save both of us.
我也不是一直这样的
I wasn't always like this.
相信我  我知道你的感受
Trust me, I know the feeling.
你看看你周围
I mean, look around you.
我们不能让发生在我们身上的坏事  决定我们是谁
We can let the bad things that happened to us define who we are,
我们要决定我们是谁
or we can define who we are.
我们得走了
We have to float more.
圣地是我的
Sanctum is mine!
越来越糟糕了
It just keeps getting worse.
不  离我远一点
JOSEPHINE II: No, no! Get away from me!
他的灵魂将永存
JOSEPHINE VII: His spirit shall live eternal.
警告  严重系统故障
COMPUTER: Warning. Catastrophic systems failure.
脑死亡
Brain death.
我们得出去  快点
We have to vent it all. Come on!
警告  内门开启
COMPUTER: Warning. Inner door is open.
如果我开着内门
CLARKE: If I leave the inner door open, everything in here will get sucked out at once, including us.
这里的一切都会立刻被抽走的 包括我们
We have to get back to my cell.
我们得回我的房间去 快点  这样我们才能自救
Come on! This is how we can save us both!
5  4  3
COMPUTER: 5, 4, 3...
约瑟芬
Josephine?
这边  我找到了另一个舱口
MAN: Hey! Over here. I found another hatch.
这边
DIFFERENT MAN: Hey! Over here!
弄掉
Clear it off.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
我就知道她会选这个
I knew she'd pick this one.
安静  他们能听到的
Quiet. They'll hear us.
快点  她无法呼吸了
OCTAVIA: Hurry. She can't breathe.
你没出现在营地 我们就感觉事情不好了
You didn't show up at the camp, we assumed the worst.
克拉克  你能走吗
Clarke, hey. Can you walk?
加百利  帮我一下
Gabriel, come on. Help me.
加百利
Gabriel?
约瑟芬
Josephine?
嘿
Hey. Hey.
你还想幸福的生活下去吗
You still want to live happily ever after?
坚持住
Hold on.
克拉克怎么了
What happened to Clarke?
猩红女王  你好
Blodreina. Hi.
你们俩怎么  算了
How do you two... you know what?
没时间说这个了  帮我站起来
There's no time. Just help me up.
有我呢
GABRIEL: I got you.
趴下  别动  他们会看到我们的
Get down! Don't move. They'll see us.
救命啊
Help!
- 你干什么  - 我在这里
- What are you doing? - I'm here.
认真的吗
OCTAVIA: Seriously?
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, my love.
我不会让他们伤害你的
I won't let them hurt you.
跪下
On your knees!
奥科塔维亚  放下武器
Octavia, drop your weapon!
- 快点  - 好
- Now! - OK, OK.
听我说  她需要治疗
Look. Listen to me. She needs medical attention.
如果我不赶快动手术  她就死了
If I don't operate soon, she'll die.
别碰她  小子
Take your hands off her, cog.
别废话了
JOSEPHINE: OK. Enough talk.
把女孩子杀了  把加百利收为囚犯
Kill the girl, take Gabriel prisoner,
送我回家
and get me home.
- 加百利  - 不要不要
- GUARD: Gabriel? - GABRIEL: No, no, no, no, no.
面朝地
Face the ground.
我要带你去见你父亲
I'm taking you to your father.
为了荣耀与信念
For the glory and grace...
贝拉米
Bellamy.
当然是这样了
Because of course it is.
带她走
Take her.
快点
Come on.
走了
Hey, hey. Let's go.
等等  我腿没知觉了
Wait. No. I can't feel my legs.
快点  走
Yeah. We have to hurry. Come on.
我马上来
BELLAMY: Right behind you.
你回到圣地去
Go back to Sanctum.
告诉拉塞尔  如果他敢伤害我们任何一个
You tell Russell if he hurts any of my people
他就再也见不到他女儿了
he'll never see his daughter again.
快去
Go!
贝拉
Bell...
我不会让你带走这孩子的
I won't let you take this child.
在我把这链子套在你脖子上之前
Get the hell out of my sight
赶紧滚出我的视线
before I wrap this chain around your throat for disobeying me!
天啊
ABBY: Oh, for God sakes,
把火焰从她脑子里拿出来吧
just take the damn Flame out of her head.
不行的  她把口令给改了
I can't. She changed the passphrase.
如果我们回到了母船上
What happens when we get back to the mothership
然后她唤醒了她沉睡的军队呢
and she wakes her sleeping army?
不能让她带领他们
We can't let her lead them.
黑暗指挥官那时候是怎么被阻止的
H-how was Sheidheda stopped in his time?
被他的看守人杀死的
EMORI: Killed by his Flamekeeper,
反正传说是这样的
or so the story goes.
其实是他的第四任看守人杀的
GAIA: His fourth Flamekeeper actually.
前面三个都被他杀了
He murdered the first 3.
等一下  你不要想着
Hold on. If you think for one second
我会让你杀了这孩子
I am gonna let you kill that child...
那你想让我怎么办
What would you have me do?
如果我们让这东西控制同一族
If we let that thing command one Wonkru,
他会让我们怀念猩红女王的
he'll make us long for the days of Blodreina.
那火焰中其他的指挥官呢
What happened to the other Commanders in the Flame?
什么都不要说
Tell that one nothing.
他们还在的  是不是
They're still in there, aren't they?
他想办法把他们隔离了
He isolated them somehow,
操控人工智能去做事
manipulating the A.I. to do it.
如果那些指挥官大脑里的代码 可以被隔离
If the code from the minds of the Commanders can be isolated,
那就也可以被删除
it can be deleted.
贝卡的笔记本呢
Where's Becca's notebook?
在机械修理店里  但是
Back in the machine shop, but...
把门打开
MAN: Open it up.
道德不代表永生  对吧
Morality not immortality, huh?
时间到了  走吧
MAN: Time's up. Let's move.
看来我是那个幸运赢家
MURPHY: Well, looks like I'm the lucky winner.
计划有变
Change of plans.
拉塞尔·莱特伯恩七世  圣所的救世主
Russell Lightbourne VII, savior of Sanctum,
下达了一个新的命令
has issued a new order.
那个孩子可以幸免
The child is spared,
但你们剩下的人将因自己的罪行 被烧死在火刑柱上
but the rest of you will burn at the stake for your crimes.
什么
What?
走吧
Let's go.
拜托  这不是原本的计划
- Wait, wait, wait. This wasn't the plan. - Come on.
- 你别碰我  - 放开我  住手
Get your hands off me. - Get your hands off me. - Let go. Stop!
再见了  赛达
Good-bye, Seda.
我带着一个梦想来到这个世界
RUSSELL: I came to this world with a dream.
基于那个梦想  我们创造了圣所
From that dream, we created Sanctum
给你们每个人赋予了生命
and gave life to every single one of you.
西蒙妮和我爱护你们  正如我们爱护你的父母
Simone and I have loved you as we loved your parents
以及你们父母的父母那样
and their parents before them.
你们都是我们的孩子
You are our children,
这200年来  我们都在教导你们不要战斗
and for 200 years, we taught you not to fight,
我们教导你们要学会原谅
we taught you to forgive,
但有些事情是
but there are some things for which there can be
无法原谅的
no forgiveness.
你为什么不告诉我他们全部将被处决
Why didn't you tell me it would be all of them?
我之前不知道
I didn't know.
约瑟芬不见了
RUSSELL: Josephine is missing,
被他们带出了护盾
taken by them beyond the shield,
恐怕她现在已经死了
and must now be presumed to be dead.
我向所有神祈祷  她有一天能回来
I pray to all that is holy that she will someday return.
该死的  不要再动了
Damn it. Stop moving.
他在说谎
He's lying!
- 他们不是神  - 闭嘴
- EMORI: They're not gods! - GUARD: Shut up!
嘿
Hey!
这些亵渎者从地球上带来的疾病
RUSSELL: Now the disease that these blasphemers
已经传播开了
brought with them from Earth has spread.
今天  我亲爱的西蒙妮也被杀害了
Today, my beloved Simone has been murdered, too,
是他们中的一个人干的
by one of our own.
我们的圣所家族被侵犯了
Our Sanctum family has been violated.
我们必须捍卫它
We must defend it.
你们必须捍卫它
You must defend it.
瞄准他了
ECHO: Got him.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这是为了我的家庭
For my family.
我们现在要做的
RUSSELL: What we do now
都是为了我们的梦想
we do for the dream that was...
曾经是圣所  将来也还会是圣所
and will again be Sanctum.
拉塞尔  你不必这么做的  拜托了
Russell, you don't need to do this, please.
拉塞尔
Russell!
想想看  你的骨头也可能会被 放到圣器里
RUSSELL: To think your bones might have wound up in the reliquary.
骨头
Bones.
等等  等等  听我说  听我说
Wait, wait. Listen, listen.
我们还可以制造夜之血脉的
We can still make Nightblood.
拉塞尔  听我说  好吗
Russell, listen to me, OK?
你还可以救你的妻子
You can still save your wife!
骨髓
Bone marrow.
他说的是实话
RAVEN: He's telling the truth.
艾比能做到的  就像她之前为克拉克做的那样
Abby can do it just like she did it for Clarke.
我们100年前就试过骨髓移植
We tried bone marrow transplantation 100 years ago.
但是失败了
It failed.
那是因为你们不知道配方是什么
That's because you don't know the formula,
如果你杀了我们  你将永远也不知道
and if you kill us, you never will.
放他们下来
Take them down.
是  先生  把他们放下来
GUARD: Yes, sir. Take them down.
我需要一个夜之血脉捐献者
I need a Nightblood donor.
你会是个很好的捐赠者
You'll do just fine.
把那个孩子宿主弄到我的实验室里去
RUSSELL: Move the child host to my lab.
艾比  没关系的
RAVEN: Abby, it's OK.
我们会给你一份材料清单
We'll get you a list of materials,
但我们需要使用电脑
but we need access to the computer.
你有24小时的时间
You have 24 hours,
否则大家都回到这里来
or we're right back here.
如果你想救玛蒂的话  把贝卡的笔记本给我弄来
You want to save Madi, get me Becca's notebook.
等等
Wait.
我们通过火焰  来净化圣所
Through fire, we purify Sanctum.
不
No! No!
两种波长  在一个大脑里
No! Two wavelengths, one brain.
你能告诉我克拉克的意识是怎么存活下来的吗
You mind telling me how Clarke's consciousness survived?
她脑袋里有个神经网
There's a neural mesh in her head.
在手术的过程中她的思维牢牢粘在上面
Her mind latched onto it during the procedure.
还挺酷的  是不是
It's pretty cool, huh?
我们能做什么呢
What can we do?
在我取出她的思维驱动后
Once I remove her drive,
我需要你在我重新启动她的心脏之前
I'll need you to quickly bandage the wound
迅速包扎伤口
before I restart her heart.
你要让她的心脏停止跳动吗
You're stopping her heart?
死亡使得她的思维回到驱动上了
GABRIEL: Death causes her mind to back up onto the drive.
我取出驱动之后  再重新启动她的心脏
I take it out, start her heart.
然后克拉克就能醒了吗
We get Clarke back?
她依靠你是正确的
She was right to depend on you.
不管你信不信  我们真的是朋友
Believe it or not, we're actually friends.
如果你们在现实世界里见面  再定论也不迟
We'll see about that if you ever meet in the real world.
现实世界
Real world?
是的  在我用她的思维驱动去争取和平后
BELLAMY: Yeah. After I use her mind drive to bargain for peace.
有什么问题吗
What's wrong?
他知道那意味着
He knows that means
我将会再次复活
I'll be resurrected again,
他不确定他能否让他们 再夺走一个无辜的生命
and he's not sure if he can let them take another innocent life.
是啊  我的死期到了
Aye, there's the rub.
在死亡的沉睡中
For in that sleep of death,
会做什么梦呢
what dreams may come?
但我猜你并不在乎这一切  是不是  老男人
But I guess what was OK for you, huh, old man?
不  我在乎
No. It wasn't.
你知道还有别的办法的
You know that there's another way.
如果你让我留着这个身体
If you let me keep this body,
谁也不用死了
nobody else has to die.
好了  别聊天了  动手吧
OK. No more talking. Do it.
我知道我做过很多坏事
I know that I've done bad things.
我全都不记得了
I don't remember them all,
但我知道你因此非常恨我
but I do know that you hate me for it.
我永远都不会恨你的
I could never hate you.
我知道
I know it.
我们还可以在一起的  亲爱的
We can still be together, my love.
我们可以把驱动取出来
We can take out he drives
就像你想的那样
just like you wanted.
我们可以一起变老
We can grow old together.
我  我爱了你几个世纪
I... I've loved you for centuries.
我们曾经幸福过
We had our time.
我现在得放手了
I have to let you go now.
好了  把伤口包扎好
All right. Cover the wound.
我们得重启她的心脏
We need to restart her heart.
她为什么还不醒
Why isn't she waking up?
等等  为什么我还在这里
Wait. Why am I still here?
因为我还在这里
JOSEPHINE: Because I'm still here.
圣所是我的
Sanctum is mine.
我利用了心脏手术修补网
I used the surgical mesh.
关于合作的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about the whole working together thing,
但我了解你  克拉克
but I know you, Clarke.
如果你回来的话  你会把圣所里每个人都杀死的
If you came back, you'd kill everyone inside Sanctum.
你就是这样的人
It's what you do.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry,
但是她的大脑不能再支持两个思维了
but her brain can no longer support two minds.
你在说什么呢  想想办法
What are you talking about? Do something.
她们都在她的大脑里
They're both still in there.
潜在的神经活动在死亡后会持续
Latent neural activity continues for a short time after death,
一小段时间  不过一旦大脑不再
but once the head stops telling the heart to beat,
告诉心脏继续跳动  一切就结束了  好吗
it's over, OK?
心脏和大脑
The heart and the head.
- 贝拉米  - 不
- Bell. - No.
我不能再失去她了
I'm not losing her again.
醒醒  克拉克  醒醒
Come on, Clarke. Come on!
克拉克  克拉克  我需要你
Clarke, Clarke, I need you.
玛蒂需要你
Madi needs you.
快醒醒
Now wake up!
贝拉米  她已经死了
Bellamy... she's gone.
不  她没有
No, she's not!
醒醒  克拉克  醒醒
Wake up, Clarke! Come on!
我不会让你死的
Gah! I'm not letting you go.
你是个战斗  给我醒来战斗
You're a fighter. Now get up and fight!
醒来战斗
BELLAMY: Get up and fight!
你没事了  深呼吸
BELLAMY: You're OK. Just breathe.
You're OK. Just breathe.
你没事了  深呼吸
深呼吸
Just breathe.
克拉克
Clarke?
大脑和心脏
The head and the heart.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177